getfreelists.com 2011-12-31

# Get Free Lists - Privacy Policy

###  Get Free Lists Privacy Policy

This policy covers how Get Free Lists Technologies Private Limited treats personal information that Get Free Lists collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Get Free Lists products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Get Free Lists does not own or control or to people that Get Free Lists does not employ or manage.

·  Get Free Lists collects personal information when you register with Get Free Lists, when you use Get Free Lists products or services, when you visit Get Free Lists pages or the pages of certain Get Free Lists partners, and when you enter promotions.

·  When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address. Once you register with Get Free Lists and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

·  This site is intended for use by persons over the age of 13. No information should be submitted to or posted on this Web site by users under 13 years of age.

·  Get Free Lists automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Get Free Lists cookie information, and the page you request.

·  Get Free Lists uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

·  If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site Get Free Lists Technologies Private Limited does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

·  We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Get Free Lists under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Get Free Lists communicate with you about offers from Get Free Lists.

·  We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

·  We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Get Free Lists' terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

·  We transfer information about you if Get Free Lists is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Get Free Lists will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. If you use a blog on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

·  Get Free Lists may set and access cookies on your computer.

·  Get Free Lists uses web beacons to access Get Free Lists cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Get Free Lists products and services.

·  We do not tie your personal information to our cookies.

·  We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

·  We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

·  The web site also uses SSL Encryption to protect all sensitive information that is collected on the web site

Haven't Got your required material? Please tell us what is required to you!
